export const QuizData = [
  
    {
        question: "What does the src attribute define?",
        options: ["Script", "Source", "Style", "Select"],
        answer:2
    },

    {
        question: "How do you represent comments in JSX?",
        options: ["// Like this", "<!-- Like this -->", " {/* Like this */}", "/ Like this */"],
        answer: 3
    },

    {
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        options:["Hyper Text Management Language", "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language", "Home Tool Markup Language", "Hyper Text Markup Language"],
        answer: 4
    },

    {
        question: "What does JSX stand for?",
        options:[ " JavaScript XML", "Java Syntax Extension", "JavaScript eXtension", "XML JavaScript"],
        answer: 1
    },
    
    {
        question: "Which tag is used to define an image?",
        options: ["<img>", "<picture>", "<image>", "<imgsrc>"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which attribute sets CSS classes in JSX?",
        options: ["cssClass", "class", "className", "styleName"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "What does Babel do with JSX?",
        options: ["Removes it", "Optimizes it", "Converts it to HTML", "Transpiles it"],
        answer:4
    },
    
    {
        question: "HTML element for inserting a line break?",
        options: ["<break>", "<br>", "<lb>", "<linebreak>"],
        answer:2
    },

   
    {
        question: "Is JSX mandatory in React?",
        options: ["Maybe", "Yes", "No", "Sometimes"],
        answer:3
    },

    {
        question: "How do you define inline styles in JSX?",
        options: ["Using the style attribute with a string", "Using the style attribute with an object", "Using the css attribute", "Using the inlineStyle attribute"],
        answer:2
    },
    
    

   
];